## **Marzet Khatit**

Junior Frontend Developer

I'm a junior frontend developer with a strong background of over four years in IT support and a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems and Technology. My professional experience includes technical support, customer care, conflict resolution, problem solving. Helping end users with software and troubleshooting network issues. During my internship and coursework I made a commercial website along with my fellow student. I got a "Responsive web design" certificate. I am currently working in tech support and learning JavaScript by myself with online courses and websites. I believe that my skills and experience make me an excellent candidate for the frontend developer position.

marzet.rock@gmail.com +79385153368 https://www.linkedin.com/in/marzet/ https://stairwaytohell.github.io/

# Work experience

## **Technical Support Specialist**

Service-partner, Krasnodar, RU (from 11/2018 to Present – 1, 5 year) IT support for food retail company

#### Webmaster

Freelance, Krasnodar, RU (from 06/2015 to 10/2018 – 3 years 10 months) Websites content and HTML/CSS code editor

## **Technical Support Specialist**

Transcard System, Krasnodar, RU (06/2016 to 03/2018 – 1 year 10 months)

IT support for Internet service provider

#### Intern

Kuban State University, Krasnodar, RU (12/2014 to 07/2015 – 8 months) Internship and thesis

## **Technical Support Specialist**

Rostelecom, Krasnodar, RU (10/2013 to 12/2014 – 1 year 3 months)

IT support for Internet service provider

#### Education

Kuban State University (2010 to 2015) Bachelor's degree Information Systems and Technology

# Certifications

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp, Issued Dec 2018

## **Skills**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, SCSS, Responsive Web Design, Figma, Technical Support

# Languages

Russian (Bilingual proficiency)
Adyghe (Bilingual proficiency)
English (Professional working proficiency)